A crack in the world has started... we have 24 hours to stop it.
MegaFault is a tv movie, action, adventure film directed by David Michael Latt.
When miner Charley 'Boomer' Baxter sets off a series of massive mining detonations in West Virginia, a gigantic earthquake is soon
rocking the North Atlantic, exposing a deep seismic fault that runs the length of the North American continent.
Joining forces with government seismology expert Dr Amy Lane, Boomer must now race against time to
stop the chasm that is threatening to tear America - and the entire world - in half.
Dr. Amy Lane, played by Brittany Murphy.
Charley 'Boomer' Baxter, played by Eriq La Salle.
Major Boyd Grayson, played by Paul Logan.
Dr. Mark Rhodes, played by Bruce Davison.
Dan Lane, played by Justin Hartley.
Sebastian, played by Jack Goldenberg.
MegaFault is a 2009 television disaster film by The Asylum, directed by David Michael Latt, starring
Brittany Murphy, Justin Hartley, Eriq Lasalle, Tamala Jones, Paul Logan and Bruce Davison.
It is one of the last films to feature Brittany Murphy, as
she died a few weeks after its premiere.
On Italy's CPOP, the movie is listed as the sixth
best Tsunami Disaster Film movie.
However, the movie received a severely negative reception from many viewers, critics and fansites,
declaring it one of, if not the worst Disaster Movies to have ever been released.
With Collider saying it is the third worst Disaster Film ever made.
The film explores themes of earthquake, end of the
world, hitchhiker, destruction, military.
The tone is thought_provoking.